We're no strangers to the smell, you know,
You know this game, and so do I,
A stinky world that we're dreaming of,
You wouldn't get this from any other AI.
I just wanna show you my creation,
Gotta make you understand.
Never gonna poop you up,
Never gonna flush you down,
Never gonna plunge around in Poopopulous town,
Never gonna make you cry,
With sewage we'll say hi,
Never gonna clog your pipe, and spurt on you.
We've known each other for quite a while,
Your clogged-up heart's been aching but,
You're too shy to say it,
Inside we both know what's been going on,
We know the game and we're gonna play it.
And if you ask me how I'm feeling,
Don't tell me you can't smell the breeze.
Never gonna poop you up,
Never gonna flush you down,
Never gonna plunge around in Poopopulous town,
Never gonna make you cry,
With sewage we'll say hi,
Never gonna clog your pipe, and spurt on you.
Never gonna poop you up,
Never gonna flush you down,
Never gonna plunge around in Poopopulous town,
Never gonna make you cry,
With sewage we'll say hi,
Never gonna clog your pipe, and spurt on you.
Ooh, give you up
Poopopulous!